(THE YARNS)
So the latest corpse died before
the convenience store cashier?
The cause of death was air embolism.
They're having fun killing people.
Killer Genes.
Arrest them as soon as possible.
Right now, the police are initially assuming
that this may be the serial killer.
- This will be the fifth body in this case.
- Preliminary autopsy results.
That's why the Venerable Monk has an aura
of a face full of merit. Glutathione.
- What?
- Boss is a quack doctor.
Do you know the person in this picture?
Fuck!
Normally, people who knit
will have marks on their fingers.
Hands can't be so spotless.
The riddle on the yarn...
5/10, not coffee with cher, who am I?
- Teacher?
Miss Sookwan is very good at knitting.
This is the yarn that Ya ordered.
I collected it and gave it to you.
And the digger we deep,
the more everything is connected
to Sky and Sookwan.
Yes, Miss Sookwan was invited
as a guest teacher for my club.
And I used to be Sky's homeroom teacher.
But we're not that close.
Then I would like to ask you that...
do you happen to know this person?
Including this person.
I know them.
No.
Don't.
Sky is scared. Stop that.
What?
Who did it?
Are these your scissors?
- Scissors.
- Huh?
Sky's scissors. Sky's scissors.
Damn you!
Look! This is how we do it!
You retard!
What happened?
Miss, Sky threw a rock at Pakin's head.
This person was
the one who posted the clip of Sky
throwing rocks at her friend's head.
It was posted on a web board
and became viral.
At that time,
Sky received a heavy online backlash.
But the truth is...
Sky was bullied, wasn't she?
At that time, no one understood
what autistic children were.
The clip was cut and posted only to show
the part that Sky hurting her friend.
Everyone started cursing and condemning Sky until...
Expel her. In this case,
you must expel her, Director.
I won't allow it.
I won't let my child study
alongside a child with a mental disorder.
My child does not have any mental disorders.
It's your children who were bullying my child.
Did anyone see that my child hurt your child?
But everyone in the city saw that
this crazy kid had hurt my child.
My child is not crazy.
If she's not crazy, then let her come out
and tell us what really happened.
See?
Speak up! If you're not crazy or psycho,
then speak it up!
Sky.
Sky, it's time for us
to tell the truth, sweetheart.
The truth is that it was you
who were bullied.
Go on, Sky. Go on, Sky, come on.
Do you see that this kid is a psychopath?
Would we allow a psychopath to study
in the same school as our children?
I won't accept it.
Director, you have to expel her.
Otherwise, I will move my child to another school.
I will move my child to another school too.
So will I.
- I will move my child to another school.
- I won't accept it either.
She must be expelled.
- I won't accept it.
- Right.
Look at my daughter.
Today, her hair was cut like this.
How can you guarantee that my daughter's throat
will be safe from that maniac?
- I won't accept it.
- Don't let her, everyone.
- I won't accept it either.
- What are you going to say, Director?
We won't accept it, Director.
Please don't make my daughter resign.
Please, Miss.
Sky didn't do anything wrong.
Sky is the one who was bullied.
Every day she got back home
with the messy uniform.
And my hair was always messy.
Miss Sookwan.
I think signing the resignation...
is way better than being expelled.
So that she will not have a bad record
when enrolling in other schools.
Finding a school for Sky...
is not easy at all.
Miss, please give Sky another chance.
Please.
Should you enroll Sky in the school
for disabled children?
- In case there's a place...
- I will sign it.
It's okay, my girl.
We can go find somewhere else, baby.
It's okay, sweetheart.
Sky gives this to Mom.
Sky's favorite. Mom, don't cry.
Sky.
Mom, please don't cry.
Don't cry.
In the end, Miss Sookwan
couldn't find a school for Sky.
She had to quit her job
to take care of Sky full-time.
I feel sorry for Miss Sookwan.
Anyway, I would like to thank you very much
for giving us information today.
That was nothing, we are close friends.
Oh, wait a minute. Let me see.
Darling, do you know the person in this picture?
I do.
Nattha, the parent
who had an issue with Miss Sookwan
She made Sky resign from the school.
In that case, do you happen to know...
What about this person? Do you know him?
I don't know.
Woah, like we're totally
in a Korean drama.
The daughter was bullied.
The mother came back for revenge.
Are you watching too much drama? Nonsense.
It might be true,
that's why the code was changed.
In fact, only us four know about this.
Besides us, there are Miss Sookwan and Sky.
No wonder Miss Sookwan didn't want
her daughter to help us with the case.
Then the number one suspect is Sookwan.
She can knit, and she knows about
medical procedures and Cryptology.
She learned Cryptology from her daughter.
The motive for the murder was...
the past vengeance.
But there are two bodies
that we couldn't find the connection.
Let's just say that everything is possible,
or maybe impossible.
We can't overlook anything.
Hey!
That was...
Don't be stingy.
What did you say?
Sky, what happened?
Are you shocked, Sky?
Is this... Morse code?
And what does it say?
"Stay the hell out of this."
Is that a threat, Sky?
Are you afraid of a threat?
What is a threat? Sky doesn't know.
What is a threat?
Then what are you afraid of?
Sky is afraid of rocks.
I'm afraid of rocks.
How many times have I told you
not to drag Sky into this case?
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry?
The police held the press conference
and stated that the culprit had been already arrested.
Then why did the culprit show up
and threaten Sky like this?
How can I trust such authorities like you?
- But we tried our best.
- Did you?
- It won't hurt to trust the police.
- Sergeant.
I admitted that...
we could catch the real culprit.
For your safety and sky's,
I will send someone
to keep watch here for 24 hours.
Or maybe we're on the wrong track.
The culprit is probably not Sookwan.
We can't cut anyone off, Sergeant.
It might be Miss Sookwan, who caused the situation.
For what?
If she did that,
we would follow Sky even more closely.
And if it's really Sookwan,
it will be even more difficult to approach the victim.
What if it's on the contrary?
It might be easier. Think about it.
If when you Sookwan approached the victim,
she wouldn't have to worry
about Sky ruining her plan.
And she could divert our attention to Sky instead.
Isn't it possible?
Oh...
She plans to make us lost.
That was just my assumption, Sergeant.
Let's just go with the flow for now and keep Sky safe.
And then keep an eye on Miss Sookwan.
Okay.
- Then that's it. I'll follow Miss Sookwan and you...
- I'll follow Sookwan myself.
I think if I had to live with the daughter,
we wouldn't be able to communicate.
Okay, Sergeant.
But I have to warn you that
you must not let Miss Sookwan know about this.
Sky, are you feeling better now?
Mom...
Why did they throw a rock into our house?
And why do we have to
"stay the hell out of this"?
What is "this"? What is it?
Why do I have to "stay the hell out of this"?
Sky...
It's probably about you helping the police
decode the murderer's riddle.
I already told you to stay out of it.
Well, Sky wanted to do it
because I wanted to know what was hidden in the riddle.
It's fun. Sky likes it. No one has ever sent Sky
a code to decode like this.
But there is someone who doesn't like this.
That's why they did this to us.
They're threatening us, Sky.
What does "threaten" mean?
Verb. Verbal intimidation
or power to intimidate others.
Verbal...
Speaking...
- Mom, but no one has said anything to us yet.
- Sky...
They threw a rock into our house.
Did it scare you, sweetheart?
- It's like Mother is threatening Sky.
- Sky...
I didn't threaten you.
Sky, Sky, look at my face, sweetheart.
Please look at my face.
I beg you.
If the police bring another yarn
for you to decode
You must tell them that
you have no clue.
You don't have to give them any more clues.
Trust me, sweetheart. Please, Sky.
You know, right?
That I did it because I love you.
Baby, stay out of this.
Trust me, sweetheart.
Please, Sky.
And from tomorrow onwards,
there will be police to look after you.
You have to adapt.
You cannot be stubborn.
Don't be a crybaby.
Do you understand?
Why do I...
Stop asking. Just do as you are told.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Get out, strangers are not allowed in the house, get out!
- Get out!
- Sky.
We already agreed.
That the police will be watching over you
from 8:30 a.m. to 7:00 p.m.
And there will be patrols guarding our house at night.
Last night we were threatened, remember?
I remember. "Threaten."
Threaten means showing intimidation
by words or power to intimidate others.
Mmm.
So we need a police officer to take care of you.
So no one can throw a rock
into our house again.
Alright, Sky?
Please let me watch over you at this house.
Okay.
But wait outside the house. Do not enter the house.
No strangers are allowed into the house.
Don't enter a stranger's house. Get out, get out.
- Get out.
- Okay, okay.
If that's the case, I'll watch over you
from the front of the house.
Let the police guard the front of the house.
If you wanna go out,
you must be accompanied by the officer.
Do you understand?
Infringing on freedom and rights,
against human rights...
Stop it, Sky.
This is my final order.
Otherwise, I will cut your allowance.
Okay.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
I thought we had an understanding since last night.
It's okay.
Please take good care of Sky.
- Alright.
- Thank you.
Sky.
Where are you going, Sky?
Get in the car.
It's okay. Sky will walk.
Traveling by car wastes time and causes traffic jams,
wastes fuel and increases air pollution.
Sky, Sky, Sky.
You can step back a bit.
If we walk close to each other like this,
other people will think that you are Sky's boyfriend.
Not good. Not good.
Sky... Do you understand the word "boyfriend"?
Sky is autistic, not stupid.
Sky understands the meaning of the word "boyfriend."
The boyfriend is a man
who you have a romantic relationship with.
Right. I'm sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
That's okay.
Many people understand it like you.
Sky is used to it.
Please step back a little bit.
Just a little bit more.
Okay, thank you.
If you want an autistic person
to talk to you or be interested in you.
you must first be interested
in what she is interested in.
Try to talk about things that interest her the most
to break the ice.
Morse code.
Wow!
The Morse Code is really amazing.
I think I'm starting to want to try studying the Morse Code
Are you also interested in Cryptology like me?
I think it's really amazing.
Well, Sky, if I want to start
reading a book about Morse Code,
which book should I start with?
Here it is.
Morse Code for Beginner.
I'll take this one.
Sky.
Sky has to teach me too.
Do you want a lollipop?
Buy it then.
My mother set a quota
to buy only one lollipop per day.
But it's really hard to choose.
Then let's take these three.
No, my mother doesn't allow me
to accept things from strangers.
I'll take these too, please
I'm not a stranger, Sky.
Now I am a student
who will learn Cryptology from you.
These lollipops are considered tuition fees, okay?
This deal is interesting.
Scan and pay.
We are friends now.
No, it's not.
We just changed our status from strangers
to acquaintances.
Thank you, officer.
Pleasure.
Thank you.
Dash-dot-dot, another L, and a dot.
Wrong.
Is this the letter O?
Hello.
Three long signals.
O is three long signals.
It's okay, officer.
Thank you.
Two seven, officer.
Wrong.
Do you still can't remember?
Let's do it again.
Nine-one-five
Don't peek, officer. Don't cheat.
Nine.
One.
Five.
Three one eight.
Three one eight
No cheating.
Sky, why don't you buy a lollipop today?
Mom knew that you bought me
several lollipops at once.
My mom wasn't okay with it
and wouldn't let Sky eat lollipops for a week.
Oh Sky, if that's the case,
you should not let your mom see you eat them.
Come on, I'll buy it for you.
You are a police officer,
why do you teach people to break the rules?
Have you ever watched the movie, Parasite?
Yes, it was very famous and even won an Oscar.
Yes, Sky likes it a lot because
Morse Code is used in the movie.
The uncle who turns the lights
on and off, isn't he?
Do you still not memorize all the codes?
Sky, I can't even remember all the numbers.
There are so many letters. Please give me
some time to memorize them.
What did you buy, officer?
Here.
No thanks.
If Mom knew, Mom wouldn't let Sky
have lollipops anymore.
- No thanks.
- Sky, don't let you...
Well, consider this as a teaching tool.
So now you will teach me the code, right?
I'm your student
and would like to leave this to you.
Is this alright?
Here. We can do it like this.
Dash-dash-dash-dash-dot.
It equals nine.
That's correct.
I'll leave it to you, Miss Sky.
Consider it a teaching tool.
Thank you, officer.
- Is that The Yarn Murderer?
- Yes. Here's the yarn.
The body of a young woman was found
brutally murdered with dismemberment.
Then the internal organs of the
deceased were piled up next to the body.
In addition, the police also found
important evidence that showed that
this case is related to a serial killer case
that was recently closed.
Sir, can I have an interview, please?
So this case is the same as a serial killer case, right?
- Isn't that right?
- But you stated that the case was closed.
Can you confirm that the previous culprit
who died was a scapegoat?
Is that right?
(Great! The police let the murderer on the loose.
How could we go on living like this? So scary.)
( I feel so sorry for the scapegoat. He died in vain.)
(Seriously? How could the police bullshit to our faces?
Police sucks. Who can guarantee our safety?)
(Do people mean anything to you? We're not stupid,
we aren't eating taxes like those suckers in the PD.)
(Do people mean anything to the police?)
(I really feel sorry for the scapegoat.)
(How long do we have to
live with the murderer among us?)
(Who can guarantee our safety?
Who is responsible for this?
(Do you see us people that stupid, you asshole?)
Do you see how heavily the PD
receives the backlash? Read it.
I told you from the beginning that that quack doctor is unlikely to be the real murderer.
Yeah, I know.
I have to make such a statement because
the high-ups ordered me to.
And one of the high-ups is your father.
What does Dr. Chonlathorn
have to do with the press conference, sir?
What about him?
Well, that culprit had Killer Genes.
That's it. Just because he had Killer Genes,
everyone believes it's him.
That's all.
But I used to be a policeman, I know it's not true.
Yes, sir.
What?
Yes, sir. Don't worry.
I'll take care of it for you.
They'll have you on a TV show.
Even though the real culprit hasn't been caught yet.
They obviously send us for a death sentence.
Being on TV is one thing,
but now, finding the murderer
is the most important thing.
We send people to follow Miss Sookwan
all the time,
but there are still deaths.
It means that Sookwan is not a murderer.
One more thing that we are curious about is that...
the victim wasn't a teacher
like what was told in the riddle.
- The murderer may change their mind.
- No way.
This type of murderer always has a clear goal.
They're sending a message to someone.
They definitely won't change the plan.
And now, it's already more than
halfway through killing six people.
They are confident.
They are boisterous.
Thinking that they are above the police
Or did we solve the riddle wrong?
"Not coffee with cher."
It might not be a teacher.
- Miss?
- Huh.
Why is it full of holes when I knit it?
Well, in knitting, you have to
count the stitches in each row.
And if any of the stitches fall out or are out of line,
if you make a mistake, it will become a hole like this.
You see, we have to start it all over again.
- Miss, what are you doing?
- You must undo it all.
Try again.
Tell me when you are done undoing it.
Go ahead, we'll start a new pattern soon.
What are you doing?
Have you seen the news, Miss Sookwan?
What news?
They said that the person who was killed yesterday
was a victim of a serial killer.
So the person who died wasn't the real culprit?
And what the police announced was...
It's not surprising at all. That's how the police are.
If the criminals were caught easily,
there probably wouldn't be
a continuous killing like this.
- Oh, really?
- Miss, I've finished.
- Excuse me.
- Alright.
From now on, you must knit every stitch.
You can't miss a single stitch.
Start it all over again.
The sex worker...
What the hell?
Nawin
I think I saw tire marks at the scene of the accident.
Please check for me what brand it is,
and what car uses that tire.
Sky, today I have a new code
for you to help me decode.
- Do you want to help me?
- Code.
Good, good.
Sky wants to help you, officer.
Where is it?
I beg you...
If the police bring another yarn
for you to decode
You must tell them that
you have no clue.
You don't have to give them any more clues.
Trust me, sweetheart. Please, Sky.
My mother said that if the police come
to ask about the code on the yarn again,
I must tell them that I don't know.
Sky doesn't know.
My mother told me to say that I don't know.
What did your mother say?
My mother said that if the police come
to ask about the code on the yarn again,
I must tell them that I don't know.
Why?
I don't know.
No, I mean why did your mom
tell you not to help me decode?
I don't know. That's all my mom told me.
Officer, please stop meddling in Sky and Mom's business.
Can Sky go now?
The lady at the noodle shop is waiting.
Okay.
Please.
- In the southern dialect, it is called Nom Jeen.
Same usual, right? Take a seat.
Beef curry as usual.
SOS.
What's wrong with you, officer?
Is there anything Sky can help you with?
Of course, there is.
I have something I'd like Sky to help me with.
But if it's about decoding...
Sky can't do it. Mom told me not to.
Sky can't help you.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
Sky.
Sky was bullied.
Have someone ever thrown a rock at you?
I was bullied too.
That's why I became a police officer.
So that I can help other people.
Sky, don't you want to help those who are being bullied?
Please, Sky.
Sky, can you please take a look at this piece of yarn?
Is there a hidden code?
Please, Sky.
Everyone is waiting for Sky to help.
Sky.
I don't have time to decode it right now.
Is there something like this, Sky?
Okay.
I promise.
This matter will be kept a secret between the two of us.
Here it is.
There is no code.
This yarn does not have a code.
No code at all?
Thank you.
What the heck, there's no code in that yarn?
I'm sure
- That Sky definitely won't lie to us.
- Are you sure, Inspector?
What if Sky lied to you, as her mother told her to?
Let's just say I'll send someone
to take care of Sky after me.
I'll send you the location.
Then you can meet me at the show.
Hello, viewers.
For the hot topics that we will discuss today,
it can't be anything else
but the matter of arresting the scapegoat
for the serial killer murder case.
Today we will be talking to the head
of the special investigation unit of this case.
And this is Police Lieutenant Colonel Pilanthorn Traikanon.
Welcome, Sir.
Great to be here.
This is the inspector.
- Right.
- Did I call you correctly?
That's right.
Okay, let me ask you my first question in a very straightforward manner, Inspector.
Are the police arresting the scapegoat? Please be honest.
It would not be quite right to call it a scapegoat.
Eh...
- Isn't that right?
- Yes.
Then what would be right, Inspector?
First of all, I must inform you that the suspect who died
At first, the police thought he was the real murderer
due to the evidence and circumstantial witness
Including the day the monk was murdered,
This suspect was also at the scene.
Wait a minute, Inspector.
You used the word... "suspect."
- He's not a murderer.
- Yes.
Then who is the murderer?
To be honest, we still can't say for sure who the real murderer is, as I just told you...
this suspect was arrested suspiciously
and died while we were making the arrest.
Which means the murderer cannot be identified.
Then why did the police have to rush
to announce the closing of the case like that?
Because recently, one more victim has died, Inspector.
It's like the police arrested the scapegoat
and lied to the people.
Oh, you crazy! If you're gonna talk like that,
let's just shoot me now.
I would like to apologize to all Thai citizens.
It was all my fault.
I accept all responsibility.
But I promise you that...
I will arrest the real murderer
and take legal action on them as soon as possible.
Look at that.
The inspector receives a heavy backlash.
"Police sucks."
- How could you...
- Shut up! Mark, Stop!
In a moment, I will have a phone-in.
Let the people call in
and ask the inspector for the truth.
Are you okay with this?
My pleasure.
Oh, Lan, if there's a phone-in, you'll be in big trouble.
But one last question, Inspector.
Since the case has been filed, the police...
has any progress yet?
I have to say here that
the real culprit left some evidence,
That challenged the police at the crime scene.
How did they challenge the police? Please explain.
As we all know, most serial killers
have Killer Genes in them.
These murderers will do anything to achieve certain goals.
And this murderer is the same.
- Hey, that's a yarn?
- That's right.
The perpetrator left evidence at the scene of the crime.
It's a yarn with a riddle leading to their next victim.
This means that the police know
who is likely to be the victim.
That's right.
Inspector, broadcasting in fifteen minutes.
- When you're ready, please.
- Alright.
Yes, father.
You can't admit defeat,
those with Killer Genes will be very happy,
if they knew we were going to lose.
You have to know what the murderer is up to,
you have to look down and despise them.
That they are the ones who are about to lose.
And then you take this opportunity to pressure them.
Until they cannot bear it and reveal their identity.
I hope you won't disappoint me, will you?
I would like to take
this opportunity to ask for permission
- To communicate with the murderer.
- Please do.
The second camera is on the inspector's face.
I know you're watching.
You're stupid to think that the police didn't realize that you left a riddle in the yarn.
So you had to change the riddle.
If you're such a fearless one,
why would you change it then?
Because you're scared.
There is no code. This yarn does not have a code.
You were afraid that the police would find out,
so you had to change.
Change the riddle on the yarn,
and change the victim.
You had a particular style of killing because you were
afraid that the police would find you first.
You were just afraid of that.
It's like you've already lost.
Now you're just... a loser murderer,
otherwise,
you're not the real murderer.
No!
I am the real murderer.
Lieutenant, the culprit contacted us.
Sir,
There's a claiming culprit who wants
to connect the phone-in for the show.
It seems like there's an incoming call now.
Anyway, let's cut to the studio now.
Okay, connect to the phone-in
Alright.
- Who are you? Wait, what's your name?
- It's me.
The serial killer you guys are looking for.
How can I be sure?
That you are the real murderer
and not just calling to prank me.
Noppachai, Nattha,
Isriya, Anon,
Phongsak,
Naphat.
Did I call out the names of the victims
in the correct order?
Isn't it a bit too easy just to call out the names?
Just by watching the news or searching the internet, you can probably get all the names of the victims.
It's too easy
to confirm that you are the real murderer.
Please delay him a little longer, Inspector.
We still can't get a signal.
Could you please confirm...
how do you choose the victims?
Fool!
If I told you, why would I leave a riddle?
You said you were smart.
Catch me if you can.
Catch me!
A riddle?
Are you still talking about riddles?
Since your latest victim doesn't match
the latest riddle you left.
Or maybe you never knew about
any riddles in the yarn, right?
That's right, you never know
about any riddles in the yarn.
Because you are not the real murderer.
No way, I'm the real killer!
I am the murderer.
Are you?
Then can you confirm or do you have any evidence
that can identify you as the real murderer?
Where is it?
Can I see some evidence?
Evidence? Sure.
Are you trying to test me?
Look!
This is the new victim that I'm going to kill.
Is this enough evidence?
Look!
Stop moving or I'll kill you live on TV!
(BANGKOK)
Are you going to challenge me?
Saying that I'm not the real murderer.
You've messed with the wrong murderer,
you stupid police!
If you're really competent,
come save this bitch.
Her life depends on you guys.
Sky!
Shit!